meditech.com 2019-03-31

# MEDITECH's Privacy Policy | MEDITECH

This Privacy Policy describes how Medical Information Technology, Inc. (“we”, “us” or “MEDITECH”) may collect, use, and share information about you (“you” or “user”) that we obtain through www.ehr.meditech.com (“MEDITECH Website”). By using the MEDITECH Website, you consent to this Privacy Policy and the terms herein. MEDITECH may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. It is your responsibility to check this webpage periodically to see if any terms have been changed or modified. Your continued use of the MEDITECH Website constitutes your acceptance of any updates to this Privacy Policy.

## How does MEDITECH collect your information?

MEDITECH collects information from you in three ways: (1) directly from you, (2) from MEDITECH web server logs, and (3) cookies.

  1. **Information That You Give Us**  
We obtain information about you when you use the MEDITECH Website, when you contact us about products and services, when you send us a message, or when you choose (opt-in) to subscribe to our blog, newsletter, or event notification emails. In these cases, you decide what and how much information you want to share.
  2. **MEDITECH Web Server Logs**  
An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. IP addresses allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. MEDITECH collects IP addresses in order to conduct system administration and site analysis, to improve functionality and usage of the MEDITECH Website.
  3. **Cookies**  
For information about cookies, see [MEDITECH’s Cookie Policy](https://ehr.meditech.com/cookie-policy).

## What information is MEDITECH collecting?

The information we collect might include:

  * First and last name
  * Physical address
  * Email address
  * IP address
  * Browser type and version
  * Data about the equipment used to visit the MEDITECH Website
  * Patterns of searching and browsing on the MEDITECH Website

## How does MEDITECH use your information?

We may use your information:

  * to improve the functionality and usage of the MEDITECH Website
  * to facilitate MEDITECH’s own marketing, promotional, and informational purposes
  * to track the popularity of features on the MEDITECH Website and to guide the development of new ones
  * to identify the types of devices our visitors use so that we can improve and optimize our systems

## Will MEDITECH share your information?

We will never sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others.

MEDITECH engages certain service providers, such as [Hubspot](https://hubspot.com/) and [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics), for purposes of tracking and associating Internet search and browsing behavior with our advertisements, and to provide functionality on the MEDITECH Website. We enable these service providers to use tracking technologies on, or in conjunction with, the website. The use and collection of information by these service providers is governed by their respective privacy statements, and thus is not covered by this Policy. To read more about their respective policies, check out [Google Analytics Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html), [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy), and [Hubspot Privacy Policy](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy).

In addition, we may share MEDITECH Website usage information with these service providers, who are responsible for hosting the data, to identify trends and determine market focus.  Information obtained through these processes may be combined with Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address and phone number) in order to analyze our marketing efforts. We will only share Personally Identifiable Information with third party vendors, consultants, agents, partners, and other service providers with whom we contract to help us provide or improve MEDITECH services.

## Choice/Opt-In

Automated communication is restricted to only information you have requested, such as reminders for an upcoming event or webinar, or delivery of a white paper or case study. Should you desire more regular communication from MEDITECH, you can elect to subscribe to our blog, newsletter, or event notification emails. All of these features also include an opt-out function, so you can unsubscribe at any time.

## How does MEDITECH protect your information?

The security of your information and data while using the MEDITECH Website is very important to us. We implement appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on the MEDITECH Website.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the MEDITECH website and its users is encrypted and protected through an SSL secured communication channel. MEDITECH keeps up to date with the latest encryption protocols, and does not support outdated and vulnerable protocols.  

## Third-party links

The MEDITECH Website may contain links to third-party websites. These websites are governed by their own respective privacy policies. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party websites to understand their data and information collection, as well as use practices.  

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Learn more about the [GDPR and international transfers of data](https://ehr.meditech.com/international-transfers-of-data).

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of your information, please write to us by [email](https://ehr.meditech.com/contact) or contact the MEDITECH representative listed below.

Philip Polimeno  
Senior Director, Organizational Development, Governance & IT  
MEDITECH Circle, Westwood, MA 02090   
781-821-3000
